export const setsByType = [
  {
    id: "K79EOQ",
    title: "Prepositions",
    cards: [
      { front: "a", back: "to", guess: "unquizzed", hint: "", id: "GXI087" },
      {
        front: "ante",
        back: "before",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KYH160",
      },
      {
        front: "bajo",
        back: "under",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XEJ444",
      },
      {
        front: "cabe",
        back: "next to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NDC014",
      },
      {
        front: "con",
        back: "with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HWK288",
      },
      {
        front: "contra",
        back: "against",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KOE245",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        back: "of, from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BBE715",
      },
      {
        front: "desde",
        back: "from, since",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZMN828",
      },
      {
        front: "durante",
        back: "during",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ADV447",
      },
      {
        front: "en",
        back: "in, on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SYF165",
      },
      {
        front: "entre",
        back: "between",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "THD376",
      },
      {
        front: "hacia",
        back: "towards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ORF799",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta",
        back: "until",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NIZ020",
      },
      {
        front: "mediante",
        back: "by means of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GNU983",
      },
      {
        front: "para",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CCQ886",
      },
      {
        front: "por",
        back: "by, through",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DEE418",
      },
      {
        front: "según",
        back: "according to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IGN816",
      },
      {
        front: "sin",
        back: "without",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RSO260",
      },
      {
        front: "sobre",
        back: "on, about",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SCL542",
      },
      {
        front: "tras",
        back: "after, behind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZUF453",
      },
      {
        front: "a través de",
        back: "through",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JJX917",
      },
      {
        front: "cerca de",
        back: "near",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WSS420",
      },
      {
        front: "lejos de",
        back: "far from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KYH233",
      },
      {
        front: "debajo de",
        back: "under",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EUC547",
      },
      {
        front: "encima de",
        back: "on top of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OJK444",
      },
      {
        front: "delante de",
        back: "in front of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CCZ908",
      },
      {
        front: "detrás de",
        back: "behind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VNA761",
      },
      {
        front: "al lado de",
        back: "next to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UMS135",
      },
      {
        front: "enfrente de",
        back: "in front of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YRH837",
      },
      {
        front: "dentro de",
        back: "inside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WMC368",
      },
      {
        front: "fuera de",
        back: "outside of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NPQ721",
      },
      {
        front: "junto a",
        back: "next to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CSX830",
      },
      {
        front: "en cuanto a",
        back: "regarding",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EYB484",
      },
      {
        front: "a pesar de",
        back: "despite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VHS921",
      },
      {
        front: "alrededor de",
        back: "around",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SDM950",
      },
      {
        front: "antes de",
        back: "before",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZDF755",
      },
      {
        front: "después de",
        back: "after",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AXZ246",
      },
      {
        front: "durante",
        back: "during",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RSX203",
      },
      {
        front: "por culpa de",
        back: "because of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DRN275",
      },
      {
        front: "frente a",
        back: "facing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SFZ931",
      },
      {
        front: "respecto a",
        back: "regarding",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OFM648",
      },
      {
        front: "debido a",
        back: "due to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WLD514",
      },
      {
        front: "a causa de",
        back: "because of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UFH461",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "XGK714",
    title: "Pronouns",
    cards: [
      { front: "yo", back: "I" },
      { front: "tú", back: "you", notes: "informal singular" },
      { front: "usted", back: "you", notes: "formal singular" },
      { front: "él", back: "he" },
      { front: "ella", back: "she" },
      { front: "nosotros", back: "we", notes: "masculine or mixed group" },
      { front: "nosotras", back: "we", notes: "feminine" },
      {
        front: "vosotros",
        back: "you all",
        notes: "informal masculine or mixed group",
      },
      { front: "vosotras", back: "you all", notes: "informal feminine" },
      { front: "ustedes", back: "you all", notes: "formal" },
      { front: "ellos", back: "they", notes: "masculine or mixed group" },
      { front: "ellas", back: "they", notes: "feminine" },
      { front: "mío", back: "mine", notes: "masculine singular" },
      { front: "mía", back: "mine", notes: "feminine singular" },
      { front: "míos", back: "mine", notes: "masculine plural" },
      { front: "mías", back: "mine", notes: "feminine plural" },
      { front: "tuyo", back: "yours", notes: "informal masculine singular" },
      { front: "tuya", back: "yours", notes: "informal feminine singular" },
      { front: "tuyos", back: "yours", notes: "informal masculine plural" },
      { front: "tuyas", back: "yours", notes: "informal feminine plural" },
      {
        front: "suyo",
        back: "his/hers/yours",
        notes: "formal masculine singular",
      },
      {
        front: "suya",
        back: "his/hers/yours",
        notes: "formal feminine singular",
      },
      {
        front: "suyos",
        back: "his/hers/yours",
        notes: "formal masculine plural",
      },
      {
        front: "suyas",
        back: "his/hers/yours",
        notes: "formal feminine plural",
      },
      { front: "nuestro", back: "ours", notes: "masculine singular" },
      { front: "nuestra", back: "ours", notes: "feminine singular" },
      { front: "nuestros", back: "ours", notes: "masculine plural" },
      { front: "nuestras", back: "ours", notes: "feminine plural" },
      {
        front: "vuestro",
        back: "yours",
        notes: "informal plural masculine singular",
      },
      {
        front: "vuestra",
        back: "yours",
        notes: "informal plural feminine singular",
      },
      {
        front: "vuestros",
        back: "yours",
        notes: "informal plural masculine plural",
      },
      {
        front: "vuestras",
        back: "yours",
        notes: "informal plural feminine plural",
      },
      { front: "me", back: "myself" },
      { front: "te", back: "yourself", notes: "informal" },
      { front: "se", back: "himself/herself/yourself", notes: "formal" },
      { front: "nos", back: "ourselves" },
      { front: "os", back: "yourselves", notes: "informal plural" },
      { front: "se", back: "themselves/yourselves", notes: "formal plural" },
      { front: "me", back: "me" },
      { front: "te", back: "you", notes: "informal" },
      { front: "lo", back: "him/it", notes: "masculine" },
      { front: "la", back: "her/it", notes: "feminine" },
      { front: "nos", back: "us" },
      { front: "os", back: "you all", notes: "informal" },
      { front: "los", back: "them", notes: "masculine" },
      { front: "las", back: "them", notes: "feminine" },
      { front: "me", back: "to/for me" },
      { front: "te", back: "to/for you", notes: "informal" },
      { front: "le", back: "to/for him/her/you", notes: "formal" },
      { front: "nos", back: "to/for us" },
      { front: "os", back: "to/for you all", notes: "informal" },
      { front: "les", back: "to/for them/you all", notes: "formal" },
      { front: "este", back: "this", notes: "masculine singular" },
      { front: "esta", back: "this", notes: "feminine singular" },
      { front: "estos", back: "these", notes: "masculine plural" },
      { front: "estas", back: "these", notes: "feminine plural" },
      { front: "ese", back: "that", notes: "masculine singular" },
      { front: "esa", back: "that", notes: "feminine singular" },
      { front: "esos", back: "those", notes: "masculine plural" },
      { front: "esas", back: "those", notes: "feminine plural" },
      { front: "aquel", back: "that", notes: "over there, masculine singular" },
      {
        front: "aquella",
        back: "that",
        notes: "over there, feminine singular",
      },
      {
        front: "aquellos",
        back: "those",
        notes: "over there, masculine plural",
      },
      {
        front: "aquellas",
        back: "those",
        notes: "over there, feminine plural",
      },
    ],
  },
];
